# Jamie Unrau

#### FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

jamie@unrau.me

http://unrau.me

778-772-0804

### **About**

I write the words that manifest realms...
I send photons of my devising into your eyeballs...

I specialize in reponsive front-end web development, empowered by a background in graphic design, and experience with full-stack MVC frameworks

#### Skills

Python C# PHP Swift
Ruby on Rails Wordpress .NET
Javascript Coffeescript Django
Yii2
HTML ERB, HAML
CSS LESS, SCSS, SASS

Photoshop Vim
Illustrator Bash
Pivotal Tracker Netbeans
Git, GitHub Xcode
Subversion Jira

## Education

CDI College - 2006

Web Development Certificate

Canmore Collegiate High School - 2003

High School Diploma

Introduction to Interactive
Programming in Python
Coursera.org
Certificate of Completion
with Distinction

# Work Experience

## Web Developer

Project House Boutique Business Solutions Inc.

August 2016 - Current

Wordpress Theming - PHP - Javascript - HTML - SASS

At Project House, I meet with clients to discuss their website needs, work with our graphic designers to ensure the responsiveness of designs, and develop new websites for clients, mostly on the Wordpress platform. I also created a custom boilerplate Wordpress theme for us to use in the development of new websites.

## Web Development Consultant StemCell Technologies

May 2016 - July 2016

Python - Selenium - QA

I was brought on as a temporary consultant to assist in the launch of the new website. I migrated databases, wrote scripts in Python to automate various tasks, implemented a Selenium test suite to automate QA tasks, and helped deploy the new site to production.

# Software Engineer ReCollect Systems Inc.

June 2014 - Sept 2015

Custom MVC PERL Stack - Xamarin - C# - Coffeescript - HTML - LESS

At ReCollect, I created new features and diagnosed & fixed bugs for their SaaS full-stack web application and their iOS & Android apps. I also created design standards for their apps, as well as a suite of photoshop templates that enabled their customers and contractors to create artwork that complied with those standards.

# Volunteer Experience

Volunteer Mentor Ladies Learning Code

Nov 2013 - Current

With Ladies Learning Code, I train students in the basics of various programming languages and development frameworks, including Javascript, Python, and HTML & CSS.